<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1475 </DOCNO>
     The holding of <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">13.6 million</NUMEX> shares is up from a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">6.7 %</NUMEX> stake that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Burmah</ENAMEX> announced <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">SHV</ENAMEX> held as of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">last Monday</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Burmah</ENAMEX> said it had n't held any discussions with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">SHV</ENAMEX> and that `` no deal of any nature is in contemplation .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1476 </DOCNO>
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">official</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John DeVillars</ENAMEX> , asked <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Clean Harbors</ENAMEX> for more information before ruling on a permit for the site .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Clean Harbors</ENAMEX> , based in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Quincy </ENAMEX>, said it `` will proceed expeditiously '' to submit the data requested .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Alan McKim </ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief executive officer</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Clean Harbors</ENAMEX> said he was `` very much encouraged '' by the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">official</ENAMEX> 's praise of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Clean Harbors</ENAMEX> for the quality of some of the data in the report .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1477 </DOCNO>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1478 </DOCNO>
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Office of Thrift Supervision</ENAMEX> banned <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">B.J. Garman</ENAMEX> , a former <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">director</ENAMEX> of the failed <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Vision Banc Savings Association</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Kingsville</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Texas</ENAMEX> , from working in any financial <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">institution</ENAMEX> insured by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">government</ENAMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">office</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Treasury Department</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">unit</ENAMEX> that is the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">successor</ENAMEX> to the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Federal Home Loan Bank Board </ENAMEX>, said this was the <NUMEX TYPE="ORDINAL">first</NUMEX> announcement of an enforcement action since <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">this year</TIMEX> 's thrift-bailout legislation ordered that all such actions by federal banking <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">regulators</ENAMEX> be made public .
     Indeed , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">OTS</ENAMEX> said that before the law took effect <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Aug. 9</TIMEX> , it banned another `` key <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Vision Banc</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">insider</ENAMEX> '' from insured financial <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">institutions</ENAMEX> .
     That <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">individual</ENAMEX> was n't identified .
     Ms. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Garman</ENAMEX> could n't be reached for comment .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1479 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Arizona Instrument Corp.</ENAMEX> said it expects to post a <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> net loss of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">about $ 600,000</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">25 cents to 27 cents</NUMEX> a share , compared with net income of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 214,000</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">10 cents</NUMEX> a share , <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Tempe</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Ariz.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">maker</ENAMEX> of underground fuel-storage systems said the most recent period was affected by <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">customers</ENAMEX> ' problems complying with recent <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Environmental Protection Agency</ENAMEX> regulations .
     For <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the nine months</TIMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> expects to post a net loss of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">about $ 879,000</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">35 cents to 40 cents</NUMEX> a share , on revenue of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 6.5 million</NUMEX> .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">A year earlier</TIMEX> , it had a loss of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 199,203</NUMEX> or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">nine cents</NUMEX> a share , on revenue of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 7.6 million</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1480 </DOCNO>
     Growth is good .
     At least , that 's a theme emerging among many money <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> who are anxious both to preserve the handsome stock-market gains they have already achieved <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">this year</TIMEX> and to catch the next wave of above-average <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">performers</ENAMEX> .
     They are starting to buy growth stocks .
     Remember them ?
     That sort of workhorse performance sounds made to order for a time when corporate profits overall have been weakening from the brisk increases of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">recent years</TIMEX> .
     The current flood of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> reports are producing many more negative surprises than positive ones .
     The question for <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> is , how to protect these returns and yet reach a little for additional gains .
     `` I think it is a good theme for what looks to be an uncertain market , '' says <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Steven Einhorn</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">partner</ENAMEX> at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Goldman Sachs</ENAMEX> .
     Growth stocks may be as big as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Philip Morris</ENAMEX> or medium-sized such as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Circuit City Stores</ENAMEX> , but their common characteristic is a history of increasing profits on the order of <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">at least 15 % to 20 %</NUMEX> a year , money <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> say .
     `` The period when growth stocks should be performing well is when their earnings are growing at a superior rate to the general level of corporate profits , '' says <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Stephen Boesel</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">T. Rowe Price</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Growth and Income Fund</ENAMEX> .
     Growth stocks also are attractive in periods of market volatility , which many <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analysts</ENAMEX> expect in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the weeks</TIMEX> ahead as everybody tries to discern where the economy is heading .
     This kind of jumpy uncertainty reminds <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John Calverley</ENAMEX> , senior <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">economist</ENAMEX> for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">American Express Bank</ENAMEX> , of the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DURATION">1969-72</TIMEX> period , when the industrial average rolled through huge ranges and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> flocked to the shares of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> with proven earnings records , which became known as the `` nifty <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">50</NUMEX> . ''
     And they will again , say money-manager <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">proponents</ENAMEX> of the growth-stock theme .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Cabanne Smith</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> of a money management <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> bearing his name , predicts that investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> using computers to identify <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> with earnings `` momentum '' will climb on the growth-stock <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT_DESC:VEHICLE">bandwagon</ENAMEX> as the overall corporate earnings outlook deteriorates further .
     He also thinks foreign <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> , who are showing signs of more discriminate investing , will join the pursuit and pump up prices . `` We 're just seeing the beginning of a shift , '' Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Smith</ENAMEX> says .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Smith</ENAMEX> recommends <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Cypress Semiconductor</ENAMEX> that is currently showing a robust <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">63 %</NUMEX> earnings growth rate .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Sloan</ENAMEX> praises the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> as recession resistant and notes that it has an <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">annual</TIMEX> earnings growth rate of <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">32 %</NUMEX> a year over <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DURATION">the past five years</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Wellman</ENAMEX> stock closed <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> at <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">39 3\/8</NUMEX> , up <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1\/8</NUMEX> ; Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Sloan</ENAMEX> thinks that in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year</TIMEX> it could hit <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">60</NUMEX> .
     Others preach the gospel of buying only blue-chip growth stocks .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Carmine Grigoli</ENAMEX> , chief market <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">strategist</ENAMEX> for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> , who still says , `` We expect the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dow</ENAMEX> average -LCB- to be at -RCB- <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">3000</NUMEX> by <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">mid-1990</TIMEX> , '' nonetheless foresees a sluggish economy in the meantime .
     He recommends such blue-chip growth stalwarts as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Philip Morris</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">PepsiCo </ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">CPC International</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Reebok International</ENAMEX> , and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Limited Inc</ENAMEX> .
     Some money <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> are pursuing growth stocks at the expense of those that rise and fall along with the economic cycle .
     `` One of the stories of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the fourth quarter</TIMEX> is that we will get an unusual number of earnings disappointments from <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> sensitive to the economy , '' says Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Boesel</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">T. Rowe Price</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">James Wright</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief investment officer</ENAMEX> for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Banc One Asset Management</ENAMEX> , says , `` We 've been selling a disproportionate share of cyclical <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> and buying a disproportionate share of high earnings stocks . ''
     He recently trimmed his portfolio of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">International Paper</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dow Chemical</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Quantum Chemical</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">International Business Machines</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Digital Equipment</ENAMEX> .
     He is putting money in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dress Barn</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Circuit City Stores</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Bruno 's</ENAMEX> , and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Rubbermaid</ENAMEX> .
     Big cyclical <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> are using `` all the tricks they can to stabilize earnings , '' says Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Sloan </ENAMEX>.
     He cites <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">IBM</ENAMEX> , which reported a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">30 %</NUMEX> earnings decline in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the third quarter</TIMEX> , and which last week announced a <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1 billion</NUMEX> buy-back of its shares .
     `` What they are telling you is that they do n't have the ability to generate higher returns internally , '' says Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Sloan </ENAMEX>.
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">IBM</ENAMEX> says it considers its shares a good investment .
     But not all <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">strategists</ENAMEX> or money <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> are ready to throw in the towel completely on cyclicals .
     Growth stocks may underperform cyclical stocks <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">next year</TIMEX> if the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Federal Reserve</ENAMEX> begins to let interest rates drift sufficiently lower to boost the economy .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Goldman Sachs</ENAMEX> 's Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Einhorn</ENAMEX> , for one , subscribes to that scenario .
     He suggests <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> think about buying cyclical shares in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the weeks ahead</TIMEX> , as well as growth issues .
     Stock prices finished about unchanged <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> in quiet expiration trading .
     But there were fewer price swings than expected .
     Buy order imbalances on several big stocks were posted by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">New York Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> .
     But block trading desks and money <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> made a concerted effort to meet the imbalances with stock to sell , <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">trader</ENAMEX> said .
     As a result , the Dow Jones Industrial Average drifted in narrow ranges in <TIMEX TYPE="TIME">the final hour</TIMEX> of trading , and closed <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">5.94</NUMEX> higher to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">2689.14</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">New York Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> volume was <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">164,830,000</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">Advancers</ENAMEX> on the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Big Board</ENAMEX> lagged <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">decliners</ENAMEX> <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">662</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">829</NUMEX> .
     For <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the week</TIMEX> , the industrial average gained <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">119.88</NUMEX> points , or <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">4.7 %</NUMEX> , the biggest <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">weekly</TIMEX> point advance ever and a better than <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">50 %</NUMEX> rebound from the <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">190.58</NUMEX> point loss the industrial average logged <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Oct. 13</TIMEX> .
     Broader market averages were little changed in the latest session .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Standard & Poor 's</ENAMEX> 500-Stock Index gained <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.03</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">347.16</NUMEX> , the Dow Jones Equity Market Index fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.02</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">325.50</NUMEX> , and the New York Stock Exchange Composite Index fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.05</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">192.12</NUMEX> .
     That contrast was reflected in the smaller weekly percentage gains recorded by the broader averages .
     The Dow Jones Transportation Average fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">32.71</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1230.80</NUMEX> amid renewed weakness in the airline sector .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> skidded <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">21 5\/8</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">168 1\/2</NUMEX> on <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">2.2 million</NUMEX> shares .
     On <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the week</TIMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> was down <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">nearly 40 %</NUMEX> .
     The latest drop followed a decision by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Airways</ENAMEX> , which had supported the <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 300</NUMEX>-a-share buy-out offer for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> from a labor-management <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">group</ENAMEX> , not to participate in any revised bid .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Airways</ENAMEX> fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">31 7\/8</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">USA Today</ENAMEX> reported that Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Davis </ENAMEX>, who had pursued <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> before dropping his bid <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Wednesday</TIMEX> , has acquired a stake of <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">about 3 %</NUMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">USAir</ENAMEX> .
     At a meeting with <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analysts</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Petroleum</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">officials</ENAMEX> dispelled speculation that the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> may take over a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> oil <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> , according to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dow Jones Professional Investor Report</ENAMEX> .
     Both <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Unocal</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Burlington</ENAMEX> had been seen as potential <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">targets</ENAMEX> for a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Petroleum</ENAMEX> bid .
     Paper and forest-products stocks declined after <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Smith Barney , Harris Upham & Co.</ENAMEX> lowered investment ratings on a number of issues in the <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">two</NUMEX> sectors , based on a forecast that pulp prices will fall sharply .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dun & Bradstreet</ENAMEX> dropped <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">3\/4</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">51 1\/8</NUMEX> on <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1.9 million</NUMEX> shares on uncertainty about the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> 's earnings prospects .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Merrill Lynch</ENAMEX> cut its rating and <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1990</TIMEX> earnings estimate <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Thursday</TIMEX> , citing weakness in its credit-rating <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">business</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lamson & Sessions</ENAMEX> , which posted sharply lower <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> earnings and forecast that results for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the fourth quarter</TIMEX> might be `` near break-even , '' fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1\/2</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">9 1\/4</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Winnebago Industries</ENAMEX> slid <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">5\/8</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">5 1\/4</NUMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> , which reported that its loss for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the fiscal quarter ended Aug. 26</TIMEX> widened from <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> , cut its <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">semiannual</TIMEX> dividend in <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">half</NUMEX> in response to the earnings weakness .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MassMutual Corporate Investors</ENAMEX> fell <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">3</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">29</NUMEX> after declaring a <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">quarterly</TIMEX> dividend of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">70 cents</NUMEX> a share , down from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">95 cents</NUMEX> a share .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1481 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Stoneridge Resources Inc.</ENAMEX> said it will begin an offering of rights equivalent to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">2.6 million</NUMEX> common shares and valued at <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 22,750,000</NUMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Bloomfield Hills</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Mich.</ENAMEX>-based real-estate holding <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said it will offer the rights at <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 8.75</NUMEX> a share to <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">shareholders</ENAMEX> of record on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Oct. 26</TIMEX> .
     The offering is scheduled to expire on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Nov. 30</TIMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said it will use the proceeds of the offering for debt reduction and general corporate purposes , including acquisitions .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Stockholders</ENAMEX> may buy <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</NUMEX> share at the subscription price for every <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">four</NUMEX> shares of stock they own .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Stockholders</ENAMEX> who exercise all their rights may buy additional shares , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said it has an option to increase the offering by <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">up to 350,000</NUMEX> shares .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1482 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Marsam Pharmaceuticals Inc.</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">1,300,000</NUMEX> common shares , via <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Smith Barney , Harris Upham</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Massachusetts</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">Approximately $ 230 million</NUMEX> of general bonds , consolidated loan of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1989</TIMEX> , Series D , via competitive bid .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Trinity River Authority</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Texas</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 134,750,000</NUMEX> of regional wastewater system improvement revenue bonds , Series 1989 , via competitive bid .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Beverly Hills</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 110 million</NUMEX> of civic center project certificates of participation , Series <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1989</TIMEX> , via a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Goldman , Sachs & Co.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:OTHER">Broward County School District</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Florida</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 185 million</NUMEX> of school district general bonds , via a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston Corp.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Michigan</ENAMEX> -- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 80 million</NUMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Michigan First</ENAMEX> general bonds , including <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 70 million</NUMEX> of environmental protection project bonds and <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 10 million</NUMEX> of recreation project bonds , via a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Shearson Lehman Hutton</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1484 </DOCNO>
     A <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">group</ENAMEX> including <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">ESL Partners Ltd.</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Fort Worth</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Texas</ENAMEX> , investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">partnership</ENAMEX> , and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Richard E. Rainwater</ENAMEX> , a former <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">adviser</ENAMEX> to the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Fort Worth</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bass</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">family</ENAMEX> , said it reduced its stake in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Anacomp Inc.</ENAMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">3.6 %</NUMEX> of the common shares outstanding .
     An <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Anacomp</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">official</ENAMEX> said the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Indianapolis</ENAMEX> computer-services <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">concern</ENAMEX> had no comment on the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">group</ENAMEX> 's share sales .
     In <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">March</TIMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">group</ENAMEX> disclosed it held a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">7.2 %</NUMEX> stake in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Anacomp</ENAMEX> for investment purposes .
     It said then it had had and would continue to have discussions with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Anacomp</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> concerning its investment .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1485 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Home Beneficial Corp.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Richmond</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Va.</ENAMEX> , said it contracted to sell its <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">50 %</NUMEX> interest in a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Richmond</ENAMEX>-area shopping <ENAMEX TYPE="FAC_DESC:BUILDING">mall</ENAMEX> to a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">buyer</ENAMEX> that was n't identified .
     The life-insurance holding <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said the sale would result in an after-tax gain of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">about $ 32 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 3.09</NUMEX> a share , in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the first quarter</TIMEX> of
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> also said it will adopt new accounting standards in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the first quarter</TIMEX> .
     The change will result in a charge of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">about $ 8.5 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">82 cents</NUMEX> a share , because of an increase in deferred income-tax liability .
     In <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the first quarter of 1988</TIMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> earned <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 10 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">94 cents</NUMEX> a share .
</DOC>
<DOC>
     f - As of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Wednesday</TIMEX> 's close .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1487 </DOCNO>
     A <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">shareholder</ENAMEX> filed suit , seeking to block <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Unitel Video Inc.</ENAMEX> 's proposed plan to be acquired by a new <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">affiliate</ENAMEX> of closely held <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Kenmare Capital Corp.</ENAMEX> for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 15</NUMEX> a share , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 33.6 million</NUMEX> .
     The suit , which seeks class-action status , was filed in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Delaware Chancery Court</ENAMEX> .
     The complaint alleges that the price is `` unfair and grossly inadequate '' and that the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">defendants</ENAMEX> are seeking to ensure a `` lockup '' of the purchase of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Unitel</ENAMEX> , thereby discouraging other bids .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">New York</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> called the lawsuit without merit .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Shareholders</ENAMEX> are scheduled to vote on the transaction <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Nov .</TIMEX>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1488 </DOCNO>
     This <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Toronto</ENAMEX> closed-end fund cut the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">annual</TIMEX> dividend on its Class A common shares to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">one Canadian cent</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">10 Canadian cents</NUMEX> .
     It said the reduced dividend reflects the low price for precious metals .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Greg Davies</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Central Fund</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">vice president</ENAMEX> , finance , said losses for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the fiscal year ending Oct. 31</TIMEX> could be as high as <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">one million Canadian dollars</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">US$ 852,000</NUMEX> -RRB- .
     The fund last had a profit in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1985</TIMEX> .
     The new dividend rate is payable <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Nov. 15</TIMEX> to <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">holders</ENAMEX> of record <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Oct. 31</TIMEX> .
     Their <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 700 million-plus</NUMEX> in estimated paper losses easily tops the <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 400 million</NUMEX> in paper losses the takeover <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">traders</ENAMEX> , known as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">arbitragers</ENAMEX> , suffered in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1982</TIMEX> when <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Gulf Oil Co.</ENAMEX> dropped a <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 4.8 billion</NUMEX> offer for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Cities Service Co .</ENAMEX>
     In <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the six trading days</TIMEX> since the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> labor-management buy-out <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> failed to get bank financing , culminating <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> with the withdrawal of its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">partner</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Airways PLC</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> stock has plummeted by <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">41 %</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">168 1\/2</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">285 1\/4</NUMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">arbs</ENAMEX> may recoup some of their paper losses if the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> deal gets patched up again , as they did in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1982</TIMEX> when <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Occidental Petroleum Co.</ENAMEX> rescued them with a <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 4 billion</NUMEX> takeover of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Cities Service</ENAMEX> .
     In the meantime , the question faced by <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> is : What is <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> stock worth ?
     The short answer , on a fundamental basis , is that airline <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analysts</ENAMEX> say the stock is worth somewhere <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">between $ 135 and $ 150</NUMEX> a share .
     That 's based on a multiple of anywhere <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">between 8.5 to 10</NUMEX> times <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> earnings , which are estimated to come in somewhere around <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 16</NUMEX> a share <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">this year</TIMEX> .
     That 's because airline earnings , like those of <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT_DESC:VEHICLE">auto</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">makers</ENAMEX> , have been subject to the cyclical ups-and-downs of the economy .
     That analysis matches up with stock <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">traders</ENAMEX> ' reports that , despite the huge drop in the stock , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> has n't returned to the level at which it could attract buying by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">institutions</ENAMEX> solely on the basis of earnings .
     <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">One</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> , who asked not to be identified , said he believes that the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> can put together a bid `` in the <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 225</NUMEX> area , '' but that it could take <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DURATION">three to four months</TIMEX> to close .
     At that level , and given the uncertainty , he believes <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> stock should trade closer to
     Other <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">observers</ENAMEX> note that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> , having accepted a bid of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 300</NUMEX> a share , might hold out for a new bid much closer to the original level -- even if it means that the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> goes back to running the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> for a while and lets things return to normal .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> have a strong financing tool in their willingness to cut their <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">annual</TIMEX> compensation by <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 200 million</NUMEX> , and to commit <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 200 million</NUMEX> from their retirement funds .
     On <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> , they also persuaded the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> flight <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">attendants</ENAMEX> to join them .
     However , investment <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">bankers</ENAMEX> say that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">banks</ENAMEX> are n't likely to lend <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">the almost $ 5 billion</NUMEX> that would be necessary for a takeover even at a lower price without someone putting up a hefty wad of cash -- probably even greater than the <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">17 %</NUMEX> in cash put up by <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> in the leveraged takeover of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Northwest Airlines</ENAMEX> parent <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">NWA Corp.</ENAMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">July</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">Banks</ENAMEX> want to see someone putting up real cash at risk , that is , subordinate to the bank debt in any deal .
     That way , they figure , someone else has an even stronger motivation to make sure the deal is going to work , because they would be losing their money before the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">banks</ENAMEX> lost theirs .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">Banks</ENAMEX> also want to be able to call someone on the telephone to fix a problem with a deal that goes bad -- preferably someone other than a union <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">leader</ENAMEX> .
     That leaves the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> still in need of cash totaling <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">around $ 1 billion</NUMEX> -- far more than either they or the flight <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">attendants</ENAMEX> can lay their hands on from retirement funds alone .
     <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">One</NUMEX> obstacle to the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> ' finding such a huge amount of cash is their insistence on majority ownership .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Investors</ENAMEX> such as <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Marvin Davis</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Los Angeles</ENAMEX> who have sought airline ownership <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">this year</TIMEX> have insisted they , not the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> , must have control .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> could borrow against the value of their concessions , using the proceeds to buy back stock from the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">public</ENAMEX> and give themselves the majority control they have been seeking .
     But it is n't clear that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">banks</ENAMEX> would lend sufficient money to deliver a big enough price to <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">shareholders</ENAMEX> .
     The lack of any new cash probably would still leave the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">banks</ENAMEX> dissatisfied .
     In advising the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> on the various bids for the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">airline</ENAMEX> , starting with one for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 240</NUMEX> a share from Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Davis </ENAMEX>, the investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> came up with a wide range of potential values for the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> , depending on appraisal methods and assumptions .
     Using the the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">NWA</ENAMEX> takeover as a benchmark , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Sept. 14</TIMEX> estimated that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> was worth <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 250 to $ 344</NUMEX> a share based on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> 's results for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the 12 months ending last June 30</TIMEX> , but <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">only $ 235 to $ 266</NUMEX> based on a management estimate of results for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1989</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> 's estimates had been higher before <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> supplied a <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1989</TIMEX> projection .
     Using estimates of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> 's future earnings under a variety of scenarios , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> estimated <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> 's value at <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 248 to $ 287</NUMEX> a share if its future labor costs conform to Wall Street projections ; <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 237 to $ 275</NUMEX> if the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> reaches a settlement with <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> similar to one at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">NWA </ENAMEX>; <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 98 to $ 121</NUMEX> under an adverse labor settlement , and <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 229 to $ 270</NUMEX> under a pilot contract imposed by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> following a strike .
     And using liquidation value assuming the sale of all <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> assets , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">First Boston</ENAMEX> estimated the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">airline</ENAMEX> is worth <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 253 to $ 303</NUMEX> a share .
     Unfortunately , all those estimates came before airline industry fundamentals deteriorated during <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the past month</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">American Airlines</ENAMEX> parent <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">AMR</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">USAir Group</ENAMEX> , both subject to takeover efforts themselves , have each warned of declining results .
     Some <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analysts</ENAMEX> do n't expect a quick revival of any takeover by the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> .
     I do n't see anybody who 's sophisticated getting his name associated with this mess until the moving parts stop moving . ''
     In addition to the need for another cash equity <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investor</ENAMEX> , the other moving parts include : the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> themselves , who can scuttle rival deals by threatening to strike ; the machinists <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">union</ENAMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> ' longtime <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">rivals</ENAMEX> who helped scuttle the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">pilots</ENAMEX> ' deal ; and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">regulators</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Washington</ENAMEX> , whose opposition to foreign airline investment helped throw the deal into doubt .
     In the meantime , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">arbs</ENAMEX> are bleeding .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Frank Gallagher </ENAMEX>, an <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Phoenix Capital Corp.</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">New York</ENAMEX> , estimates that the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">arbs</ENAMEX> paid an average of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">about $ 280</NUMEX> a share for their <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> positions .
     That would indicate that the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">arbs</ENAMEX> have paper losses on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> alone totalling <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 725 million</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL Corp .</ENAMEX> -LRB- <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">NYSE</ENAMEX> ; Symbol : <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> -RRB-
     Business : Airline
     Common shares outstanding : <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">21.6 million</NUMEX>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1491 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Eastern Enterprises</ENAMEX> , bolstered by improved tonnages in its marine-shipping <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">unit</ENAMEX> , had a narrower <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> net loss of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.1 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">five cents</NUMEX> a share .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Last year</TIMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Eastern</ENAMEX> had a <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">quarter</TIMEX> loss of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.7 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">eight cents</NUMEX> a share .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Quarter</TIMEX> revenue rose <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">44 %</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 160.1 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 111.2 million</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year ago</TIMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Weston</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Mass</ENAMEX>. , utilities and marine-transport <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">concern</ENAMEX> said results for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the third quarter</TIMEX> , usually a money-losing one because of the seasonality of the gas business , were also aided by higher gas sales and the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">May 1989</TIMEX> acquisition of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Water Products Company</ENAMEX> .
     For <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the nine months</TIMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Eastern</ENAMEX> had net income of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 41.8 million</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.80</NUMEX> a share , up <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">23 %</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 33.9 million</NUMEX> or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.46</NUMEX> a share <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year ago</TIMEX> .
     Revenue grew <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">24 %</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 614.5 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 497.1 million</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1492 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex Computer Corp.</ENAMEX> , continuing its rapid growth while other computer <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> falter , reported an <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">87 %</NUMEX> increase in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> net income from <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> and a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">50 %</NUMEX> increase in revenue .
     Revenue was <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 111.9 million</NUMEX> , up <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">50 %</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 74.8 million</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex</ENAMEX> makes supercomputers that sell for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">up to $ 2 million</NUMEX> and has an installed base of <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">more than 550</NUMEX> systems and <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">340</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">customers</ENAMEX> world-wide .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Earlier this month</TIMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex</ENAMEX> made a bid to outflank other supercomputer <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">competitors</ENAMEX> like <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Digital Equipment Corp.</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">International Business Machines Corp.</ENAMEX> by adopting an open set of standards and introducing new hardware and software to link different systems .
     The new products allow <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">customers</ENAMEX> to add <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex</ENAMEX> machines to established systems made by other <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">manufacturers</ENAMEX> , which `` opens up a phenomenal market for us , '' said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Robert J. Paluck</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex </ENAMEX>'s <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chairman</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> and chief <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">executive</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex</ENAMEX> also recently agreed to use Posix , a standard for the computer language called UNIX .
     Most other supercomputer <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">manufacturers</ENAMEX> have yet to adopt the Posix standard , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Paluck</ENAMEX> said , adding that they prefer to maintain proprietary systems that lock in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">customers</ENAMEX> .
     `` But the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:OTHER">customer</ENAMEX> does n't want that . ''
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Convex</ENAMEX> closed in over-the-counter trading on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> at <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 15.375</NUMEX> a share , down <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">12.5 cents</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1493 </DOCNO>
     Industry <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">executives</ENAMEX> said <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Interpublic</ENAMEX> approached <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Saatchi</ENAMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">August</TIMEX> about buying its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Campbell-Mithun-Esty</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">unit</ENAMEX> , but was turned down by <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Chairman</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Maurice Saatchi</ENAMEX> .
     A <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Saatchi</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">spokesman</ENAMEX> declined to comment about <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Interpublic</ENAMEX> .
     It named a new <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief executive officer</ENAMEX> , former <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">IMS International</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">head</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Robert Louis-Dreyfus</ENAMEX> .
     In addition to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Backer Spielvogel Bates</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Saatchi</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">unit</ENAMEX> that has handled the account since <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1970</TIMEX> , the other <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agencies</ENAMEX> include <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lowe Marschalk</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">unit</ENAMEX> of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lowe Group</ENAMEX> ; <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Grey Advertising </ENAMEX>; and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">WPP Group</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Scali , McCabe , Sloves</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> .
     All <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agencies</ENAMEX> are <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">New York</ENAMEX>-based .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">Jamaica</ENAMEX> Fires Back
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Jamaica Tourist Board</ENAMEX> , in the wake of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Young & Rubicam</ENAMEX> 's indictment on charges that it bribed <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">Jamaican</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">officials</ENAMEX> to win the account in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1981</TIMEX> , released a scathing memo blaming the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> for the embarrassing incident .
     The memo attempts to remove the tourist <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">board</ENAMEX> as far as possible from the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> , which pleaded innocent to the charges .
     Among other things , the memo contends that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Young & Rubicam</ENAMEX> gave false assurances that the investigation would n't uncover any information that would `` embarrass the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">government</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">Jamaica</ENAMEX> or the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Jamaica Tourist Board</ENAMEX> . ''
     It also contends that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Young & Rubicam</ENAMEX> never told the tourist <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">board</ENAMEX> about its relationship with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ad Ventures</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">Jamaican</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">firm</ENAMEX> hired by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">AYER</ENAMEX> TALKS :
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">N W Ayer </ENAMEX>'s <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief executive officer</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jerry J. Siano</ENAMEX> , said the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> is holding `` conversations '' about acquiring <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Zwiren Collins Karo & Trusk</ENAMEX> , a midsized <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Chicago</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> , but a deal is n't yet close to being completed .
     WHO 'S NEWS :
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Shelly Lazarus</ENAMEX> , <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:AGE">42</TIMEX> , was named <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief operating officer</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ogilvy & Mather Direct</ENAMEX> , the direct mail <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">division</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">WPP Group</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ogilvy & Mather</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">agency</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1494 </DOCNO>
     A company <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">official</ENAMEX> said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Arthur Borie</ENAMEX> , until <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">January</TIMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief operating officer</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Pic 'N Save Inc.</ENAMEX> , will buy a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">20 %</NUMEX> stake in the new <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Wisconsin Toy</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">subsidiary</ENAMEX> , and will act as <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">head</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Everything 's a Dollar</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Wisconsin Toy</ENAMEX> has <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">71</NUMEX> retail <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">stores</ENAMEX> , primarily in discount settings .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Patrick Basham</ENAMEX>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1498 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Roland J. Hawkins </ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chairman</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jet Vacations Inc.</ENAMEX> , was elected to the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> of this cruise line .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> expands to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">seven</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">members</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ1499 </DOCNO>
