<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2075 </DOCNO>
     But he put off a firm decision while his <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">aides</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">legislators</ENAMEX> searched for a compromise that would tighten requirements for such abortions in a way acceptable to the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> .
     But there still may be prolonged debate and political maneuvering that holds up the <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 156.7 billion</NUMEX> funding bill for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the fiscal year that began Oct. 1</TIMEX> .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Bush</ENAMEX> has said he personally approves of abortions in the cases of rape , incest and danger to the life of the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">mother</ENAMEX> .
     But he has opposed <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Medicaid</ENAMEX> funding of abortions for poor <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">women</ENAMEX> who say they are <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">victims</ENAMEX> of rape and incest , arguing that those exceptions are enforced so loosely that they open the way for abortions for other <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">women</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2076 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">NEWSPAPERS</ENAMEX> :
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Media General</ENAMEX> said it has had inquiries from potential <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">buyers</ENAMEX> and expects to complete a sale in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1989</TIMEX> .
     It would n't discuss a price .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lee Dirks & Associates</ENAMEX> is to sell the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">chains</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2077 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">J.P. Morgan & Co.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">New York</ENAMEX> , will help the statutory <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">DFC New Zealand Ltd.</ENAMEX> to evaluate the failed investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> 's condition .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Earlier this month</TIMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Reserve Bank of New Zealand</ENAMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE_DESC:COUNTRY">country</ENAMEX> 's central <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> , appointed the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> to run the investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> and pay <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">creditors</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">DFC</ENAMEX> asked the central <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> to appoint <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> after it revised loan-loss provisions to around the same level of <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">shareholders</ENAMEX> ' funds of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">180 million New Zealand dollars</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">US$ 105.4 million</NUMEX> -RRB- .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">DFC</ENAMEX> is held <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">80 %</NUMEX> by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">National Provident Fund</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">New Zealand</ENAMEX> 's largest pension fund , and <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">20 %</NUMEX> by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Salomon Brothers Inc.</ENAMEX> , the investment-bank and securities-firm <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">subsidiary</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Salomon Inc.</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">New York</ENAMEX> .
     A <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">spokeswoman</ENAMEX> for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">J.P. Morgan</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">parent</ENAMEX> of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Morgan Guaranty Trust Co.</ENAMEX> , confirmed its appointment to assist the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> but declined to elaborate .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> said in a brief statement <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">yesterday</TIMEX> that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Morgan</ENAMEX> will help evaluate <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">DFC</ENAMEX> 's position and help determine alternatives .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">managers</ENAMEX> do n't expect to complete the evaluation until <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Nov. 30</TIMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2078 </DOCNO>
     An experimental <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:DRUG">vaccine</ENAMEX> can alter the immune response of <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">people</ENAMEX> infected with the <ENAMEX TYPE="DISEASE">AIDS</ENAMEX> virus , a prominent <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">scientist</ENAMEX> said .
     However , that does n't mean they can benefit from the <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:DRUG">vaccine</ENAMEX> .
     Its effectiveness ca n't be determined until a large clinical trial is undertaken by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Army</ENAMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">January</TIMEX> , according to <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Robert Redfield</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chief</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="DISEASE">acquired immune deficiency syndrome</ENAMEX> research at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:OTHER">Walter Reed Army Institute of Research</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Dr.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Redfield </ENAMEX>'s report on early experiments using an <ENAMEX TYPE="DISEASE">AIDS</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:DRUG">vaccine</ENAMEX> made by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MicroGeneSys Inc.</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">West Haven</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Conn.</ENAMEX> , came at a meeting of <ENAMEX TYPE="DISEASE">AIDS</ENAMEX> vaccine <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">researchers</ENAMEX> in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Florida</ENAMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">late Monday</TIMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:DRUG">vaccine</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT:OTHER">VaxSyn HIV-1</ENAMEX> , has been safely given to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">14</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">people</ENAMEX> , some of whom are experiencing substantial increases in certain antibodies .
     `` The conventional wisdom used to be that you could n't modify the immune response of an infected <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">individual</ENAMEX> '' by innoculating them with synthetic viral <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:OTHER">proteins</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Dr.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Redfield</ENAMEX> said .
     `` We 've demonstrated that you can . ''
     He said certain <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">volunteers</ENAMEX> developed kinds of antibodies associated with early <ENAMEX TYPE="DISEASE">AIDS</ENAMEX> .
     Other antibodies sparked by the preparation are of a sort rarely present in large quantities in infected or ill <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">individuals</ENAMEX> , he added .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Cross & Trecker</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Bloomfield Hills</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Mich.</ENAMEX> , machine-tool <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">maker</ENAMEX> , said the net sales price of the total transaction is <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 24 million</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Cross & Trecker</ENAMEX> said negotiations are under way for the sale of another <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">RobertsCorp .</ENAMEX>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2080 </DOCNO>
     There was also a decline in the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> 's net financial costs to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">25 million francs</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">50 million</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year before</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Matra</ENAMEX> said the sharp rise in its <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">first-half</TIMEX> earnings was based on a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">15 %</NUMEX> gain in consolidated revenue to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">10.16 billion francs</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">8.85 billion</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2082 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Rep.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hamilton</ENAMEX> said the bill will be modified substantially to call for <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">two</NUMEX> meetings <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">each year</TIMEX> between the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Fed</ENAMEX> 's open market <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">committee</ENAMEX> and the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Treasury</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Secretary</ENAMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chairman</ENAMEX> of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Council of Economic Advisers</ENAMEX> and the <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">director</ENAMEX> of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Office of Management and Budget </ENAMEX>.
     The original bill was strongly opposed by the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Fed</ENAMEX> and publicly criticized by <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">friends</ENAMEX> of the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Fed</ENAMEX> as an attempt to undermine the central <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">bank</ENAMEX> 's independence .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Fed</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">critics</ENAMEX> , however , hailed it as a long overdue attempt to bring a measure of openness and democracy to the setting of monetary policy .
     The administration <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">officials</ENAMEX> do n't ordinarily meet with the entire <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">membership</ENAMEX> of the open market <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">committee</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2083 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">B.F. Goodrich Co.</ENAMEX> said <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> profits dropped <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">34 %</NUMEX> because of lower prices for polyvinyl chloride materials , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> 's largest product group .
     Sales for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the quarter</TIMEX> slipped <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">2.7 %</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 601.3 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 618.1 million</NUMEX> .
     Polyvinyl chloride capacity `` has overtaken demand and we are experiencing reduced profit margins as a result , '' said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John D. Ong </ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chairman</ENAMEX> and chief <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">executive</ENAMEX> .
     The plastic <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:OTHER">resin</ENAMEX> is used in a wide range of products , including siding , pipe and electrical wire insulation .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Goodrich</ENAMEX> 's vinyl-products <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">segment</ENAMEX> reported operating profit for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the quarter</TIMEX> of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 30.1 million</NUMEX> , <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">less than half the $ 64.1 million</NUMEX> of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the year-earlier quarter</TIMEX> .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Third-quarter</TIMEX> operating profit of the specialty-chemicals <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> declined slightly to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 24.3 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 24.9 million</NUMEX> .
     But operating profit from aerospace products rose <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">nearly 50 %</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 15 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 10.1 million</NUMEX> .
     In <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">New York Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> composite trading , shares of the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Akron</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Ohio</ENAMEX>-based <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> fell <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.375</NUMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 49.125</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
     He succeeds <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John A. Boudreau</ENAMEX> , who resigned for personal reasons .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Tanner</ENAMEX> had been <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Penn Pacific</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">National Southwest Capital Group</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">subsidiary</ENAMEX> .
     He has also agreed to become <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">president</ENAMEX> of a new <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">subsidiary</ENAMEX> to be formed to make future acquisitions , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2086 </DOCNO>
     Spooked <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> , despite their stampede to dump takeover stocks , should hold on tight to their <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> shares .
     That 's the view of some <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analysts</ENAMEX> here who argue that <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">Britain</ENAMEX> 's leading <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">maker</ENAMEX> of luxury <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT_DESC:VEHICLE">cars</ENAMEX> still may have <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">two</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> auto <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">giants</ENAMEX> battling for it .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Yesterday</TIMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford Motor</ENAMEX> disclosed that it has raised its holding in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">10.4 %</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">5 %</NUMEX> .
     Both <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> and its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">rival</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">General Motors</ENAMEX> recently set their sights on grabbing significant minority stakes in the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">British</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's latest move increases the pressure on <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> to complete its current talks with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> quickly .
     At that point <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> may face a long , bumpy ride .
     `` This is an exceptionally odd takeover battle , '' says <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">London</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Christopher Will</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Shearson Lehman Hutton</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> topped the most-active list for the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> over-the-counter market <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Monday</TIMEX> .
     And on <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">London</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Stock Exchange</ENAMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Monday</TIMEX> , <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">18.5 million</NUMEX> shares were traded , far above the usual volume .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's share purchases undoubtedly accounted for much of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Monday</TIMEX> 's heavy trading .
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Last week</TIMEX> , many <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">shareholders</ENAMEX> took their money and ran .
     Fears that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's ardor might be cooling put <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> shares into reverse after <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> confirmed its friendly negotiations with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> .
     But <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">yesterday</TIMEX> 's announcement indicates that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> has n't lost interest .
     Both <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Shearson</ENAMEX> 's Mr . <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Will</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Stephen Reitman</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">European</ENAMEX> auto <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> at the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">London</ENAMEX> brokerage <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">firm</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UBS-Phillips & Drew</ENAMEX> , recently switched their <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> recommendations to hold from buy .
     `` Sit tight '' through the coming volatility , Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Reitman</ENAMEX> suggests , though he concedes that many small <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investors</ENAMEX> will find <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> 's zigzags `` too hard to swallow . ''
     But a crucial point is how <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> reacts when <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> , the world 's largest <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT_DESC:VEHICLE">auto</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">maker</ENAMEX> , firms up its proposed deal with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> .
     At the moment , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">executives</ENAMEX> will say little beyond reiterating their desire to raise <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> stake to <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">about 15 %</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> is expected to inject <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">roughly # 200 million</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 316 million</NUMEX> -RRB- by acquiring some <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> shares , and then win <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> 's promise of an eventual <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">30 %</NUMEX> stake .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">shareholders</ENAMEX> would have to bless such a far-reaching accord .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> might challenge the proposal by offering a full bid if <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">holders</ENAMEX> and the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.K.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:GOVERNMENT">government</ENAMEX> agreed to drop the anti-takeover barrier early .
     `` I think <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> is going to come out with full <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT_DESC:WEAPON">guns</ENAMEX> blazing , '' Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Reitman</ENAMEX> says .
     `` <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> wants -LCB- <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> -RCB- very much . ''
     <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> takeover-stock <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">speculators</ENAMEX> , who may own <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">between 20 % and 30 %</NUMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> , could give <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> enough votes to block the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> deal .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> might counterbid .
     He believes <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> 's share price could zoom to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">between # 8 and # 10</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 12.60 to $ 15.80</NUMEX> -RRB- .
     `` There 's quite a bit of value left in the -LCB- <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> -RCB- shares here even though they have run up '' lately , says <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Doug Johnson</ENAMEX> , a fund <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">manager</ENAMEX> for <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Seattle</ENAMEX>-based <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Safeco Asset Management</ENAMEX> .
     At the moment , he intends to keep the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">firm</ENAMEX> 's <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">180,000</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> shares .
     The risk is that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> 's share price could slump if <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">GM</ENAMEX> 's agreement with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> effectively locks out its <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">rival</ENAMEX> .
     `` <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's appetite to attack -LCB- <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> -RCB- could gradually wane over time , particularly if <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Saab</ENAMEX> is a reasonably attractive proposition , '' says <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John Lawson</ENAMEX> , an auto <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> at <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">London</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:OTHER">Nomura Research Institute</ENAMEX> .
     Of course , that was before <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Ford</ENAMEX> 's latest move .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Jaguar</ENAMEX> -LRB- OTC ; Symbol : <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">JAGRY</ENAMEX> -RRB-
     Net income : <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 44.9 million</NUMEX> ; or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">25 cents</NUMEX> a share
     <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">First half ended , June 30 , 1989</TIMEX> :
     Net loss : <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.7 million</NUMEX> vs. net income : <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 21.2 million</NUMEX> ; or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">12 cents</NUMEX> a share
     Averae <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">daily</TIMEX> trading volume : Ordinary shares outstanding : <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">182.9 million</NUMEX>
     NOTE : All figures are translated into <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> dollars based on current exchange rates .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2087 </DOCNO>
     No <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">replacement</ENAMEX> was immediately named .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Sloan</ENAMEX> plans to remain on the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> until his current term expires in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">April 1991</TIMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lance</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">spokesman</ENAMEX> said .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2088 </DOCNO>
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> is n't proposing a slate of its own and the other <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">four</NUMEX> current <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">directors</ENAMEX> do n't want to serve beyond the special meeting date , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Newport</ENAMEX> said .
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hollander</ENAMEX> `` is the new <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">owner</ENAMEX> and wants to exercise control , '' said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Barret B. Weekes</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Newport</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">chairman</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2089 </DOCNO>
     The <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 76.6 million</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 120.6 million</NUMEX> -RRB- in pretax profit for <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the 12 months to June 30</TIMEX> was down from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 160 million</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 252 million</NUMEX> -RRB- <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> and below market expectations of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 80 million</NUMEX> and <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 90 million</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Amstrad</ENAMEX> 's profit after taxes fell a similarly steep <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">51 %</NUMEX> , to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 51.1 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 105 million</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
     Sales edged up fractionally to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 626.3 million</NUMEX> from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY"># 625.4 million</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2091 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Microsoft Corp.</ENAMEX> 's earnings growth continued to outstrip that of most of its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">competitors</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">customers</ENAMEX> in the personal-computer industry , as it reported a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">36 %</NUMEX> jump in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">fiscal first-quarter</TIMEX> earnings on a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">33 %</NUMEX> revenue gain .
     Revenue rose to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 235.2 million</NUMEX> , from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 176.4 million</NUMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Microsoft</ENAMEX> previously indicated it would have <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a strong quarter</TIMEX> by forecasting its revenue gain on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Oct. 4</TIMEX> , causing a <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 6.50</NUMEX> a share jump in its stock .
     But its stock jumped again <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">yesterday</TIMEX> as it disclosed surprisingly strong margins on those sales .
     The stock had hit a high of <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 81</NUMEX> a share <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">early last week</TIMEX> but collapsed to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 73.50</NUMEX> in the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Friday</TIMEX> stock plunge .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> had been experiencing softening margins because of increased sales of software applications , which have lower margins than do operating systems .
     But the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> said that trend was offset in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the first quarter</TIMEX> by better economies of scale and efficiencies in manufacturing .
     As a result , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Microsoft </ENAMEX>'s cost of goods , as a percentage of sales , fell <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">17 %</NUMEX> from <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the year-ago quarter</TIMEX> and <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">13 %</NUMEX> from the previous period .
     The trend drove up the aftertax margin -- net income as a percentage of revenues -- to <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">21.1 %</NUMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the quarter</TIMEX> , compared with <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">20.7 %</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Microsoft</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">officials</ENAMEX> said the strong results also reflected continuing high demand for its software applications and operating systems .
     While it has predicted that overall growth in unit sales of personal computers is slowing to about a <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">10 %</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">yearly</TIMEX> rate , its own products are selling at a much faster rate because many are geared to the high-performance end of the market .
     That segment continues to post strong <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">quarter</TIMEX>-to-<TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">quarter</TIMEX> gains , while the low-end , or commodity segment , of the industry is experiencing sluggish growth or even sales declines .
     Compared with <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">its previous quarter</TIMEX> , the final period of <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">its 1989 fiscal year</TIMEX> , net rose <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">9 %</NUMEX> , and sales rose <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">7 %</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2092 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Control Data Corp.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Minneapolis</ENAMEX> , signed a joint development agreement with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MIPS Computer Systems Inc.</ENAMEX> to incorporate an emerging computing architecture in future machines .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MIPS</ENAMEX> is a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">leader</ENAMEX> in what is known as reduced-instruction set computing , or RISC , a technology combining microprocessors and sophisticated software .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Digital Equipment Corp.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Tandem Computers Inc.</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">NEC Corp.</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Group Bull</ENAMEX> , among others , have similar arrangements with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MIPs </ENAMEX>, based in <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Sunnyvale</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Calif .</ENAMEX>
     The accord with <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">MIPS</ENAMEX> calls for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Control Data</ENAMEX> to share its expertise in data storage , the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">companies</ENAMEX> said .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Control Data</ENAMEX> also said it is developing what it called a `` supermainframe '' computer , the <ENAMEX TYPE="PRODUCT:OTHER">Cyber 2000</ENAMEX> , intended for <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">scientists</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">engineers</ENAMEX> and other <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">users</ENAMEX> of generalpurpose high-performance computers .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2093 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX>'S STOCK SKIDDED <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">an additional $ 24.875</NUMEX> , to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 198</NUMEX> , as <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">British Airways</ENAMEX> indicated it may balk at any hastily revised version of the aborted <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 6.79 billion</NUMEX> buy-out of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">United Air</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">parent</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> has fallen <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 87.25</NUMEX> , or <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">31 %</NUMEX> , in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the three trading days</TIMEX> since disclosure of the buy-out 's collapse jolted the stock market .
     Meanwhile , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">investor</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Marvin Davis</ENAMEX> said he remains interested in <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> , but he dropped his earlier <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 300</NUMEX>-a-share back-up bid .
     Stock prices fell broadly in heavy trading , dominated by futures-related program selling and further declines by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">UAL</ENAMEX> and other airline stocks .
     Bond prices ended lower after an early rally , while the dollar was mixed .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> trade deficit swelled to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 10.77 billion</NUMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">August</TIMEX> , prompting worries that the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE_DESC:COUNTRY">nation</ENAMEX> 's export drive had stalled .
     An <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> called it <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">one</NUMEX> of the worst trade reports since the dollar bottomed out in
     Industrial output fell <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">0.1 %</NUMEX> in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">September</TIMEX> , the latest sign manufacturing is slowing .
     An <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">analyst</ENAMEX> cited weaker capital spending and exports .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Bankers Trust</ENAMEX> added <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 1.6 billion</NUMEX> to reserves for Third World loans , the latest big <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">bank</ENAMEX> to take such a step .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Manufacturers Hanover</ENAMEX> had a loss due to a big reserve addition .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Tele-Communications</ENAMEX> agreed to buy <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">half</NUMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Showtime Networks</ENAMEX> from <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Viacom</ENAMEX> for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 225 million</NUMEX> .
     The move could pose a new challenge to <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Time Warner</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Home Box Office</ENAMEX> .
     The <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">CFTC</ENAMEX> plans to curb dual trading on commodities markets , in which <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">traders</ENAMEX> buy and sell both for their own account and for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">clients</ENAMEX> .
     The move is likely to anger <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">traders</ENAMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">FDIC</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Chairman</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Seidman</ENAMEX> said that <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Lincoln Savings & Loan of California</ENAMEX> should have been seized in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">1986</TIMEX> to contain losses he estimated will cost <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">taxpayers</ENAMEX> <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">as much as $ 2 billion</NUMEX> .
     A <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 67 billion</NUMEX> spending bill was approved by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">House</ENAMEX>-<ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Senate</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">conferees</ENAMEX> that includes major provisions affecting the federal mortgage market .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Hooker</ENAMEX> 's <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">U.S.</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">unit</ENAMEX> is expected to agree in principle <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">this week</TIMEX> to sell its <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Merksamer Jewelers</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">chain</ENAMEX> to <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">management</ENAMEX> , according to <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">executives</ENAMEX> .
     The deficit-reduction bill became snagged over efforts to streamline the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">House</ENAMEX> version of the legislation in advance of a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">House</ENAMEX>-<ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Senate</ENAMEX> conference .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Integrated Resources</ENAMEX> said talks have ended with another potential <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">buyer</ENAMEX> of its core businesses .
     <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">Three</NUMEX> big <ENAMEX TYPE="SUBSTANCE:DRUG">drug</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">makers</ENAMEX> posted robust <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">third-quarter</TIMEX> earnings .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Merck</ENAMEX> 's profit climbed <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">25 %</NUMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Warner-Lambert </ENAMEX>'s <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">22 %</NUMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Eli Lilly</ENAMEX> 's <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">24 %</NUMEX> .
     Markets --
     Commodities : <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Dow Jones</ENAMEX> futures index <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">129.72</NUMEX> , unchanged ; spot index <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">129.97</NUMEX> , off <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.19</NUMEX> .
     Dollar : <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">142.75 yen</NUMEX> , up <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.95</NUMEX> ; <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">1.8667 marks</NUMEX> , off <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">0.0018</NUMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2094 </DOCNO>
     Mr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ely </ENAMEX>, <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:AGE">57 years old</TIMEX> , temporarily increases the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> to <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">seven</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">members</ENAMEX> .
     However , <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">director</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Thomas O'Rourke</ENAMEX> has said he wo n't seek re-election at the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> 's <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:OTHER">annual</TIMEX> meeting <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">next month</TIMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2095 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">BroadBeach Associates Inc.</ENAMEX> , the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Los Angeles</ENAMEX> investment <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">partnership</ENAMEX> whose <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 62</NUMEX>-a-share bid for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">McGill Manufacturing Co.</ENAMEX> was topped recently by a competing offer from a <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">Swedish</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">concern</ENAMEX> , disclosed that it sold its entire <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">7 %</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">McGill</ENAMEX> stake .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">McGill</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Valparaiso</ENAMEX> , <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:STATE_PROVINCE">Ind.</ENAMEX> , ball-bearing <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">manufacturer</ENAMEX> , had rebuffed <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">BroadBeach</ENAMEX> 's proposal .
     It has since asked <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">holders</ENAMEX> not to immediately tender their shares under a recent <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 72</NUMEX>-a-share , or <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 104 million</NUMEX> , bid from <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">AB SKF</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:COUNTRY">Sweden</ENAMEX> , until <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">McGill</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">directors</ENAMEX> have completed their evaluation .
     In a <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:GOVERNMENT">Securities and Exchange Commission</ENAMEX> filing , <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">BroadBeach</ENAMEX> said it sold the <NUMEX TYPE="CARDINAL">101,000</NUMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">McGill</ENAMEX> shares for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 7.3 million</NUMEX> in a private transaction on <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">Oct. 12</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">BroadBeach</ENAMEX> did n't identify the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">buyer</ENAMEX> of the shares , but the date of the selloff followed by <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DURATION">one day</TIMEX> the <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">Swedish</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">concern</ENAMEX> 's tender offer , and the indicated price of the shares sold equals <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">SKF</ENAMEX> 's <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 72</NUMEX>-a-share tender offer price .
     A <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">BroadBeach</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">spokeswoman</ENAMEX> said the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> sold the stock in the open market and thus could n't identify the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">buyer</ENAMEX> or <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">buyers</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2096 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Luis Nogales </ENAMEX>, <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:AGE">45 years old</TIMEX> , has been elected to the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">board</ENAMEX> of this <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">brewer</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> WSJ2097 </DOCNO>
     <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Hachette S.A.</ENAMEX> , a <ENAMEX TYPE="NORP:NATIONALITY">European</ENAMEX> media and publishing <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">group</ENAMEX> , reported a small rise in its attributable <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">first-half</TIMEX> group profit , excluding exceptional items , to <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">133.8 million francs</NUMEX> -LRB- <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$ 21.1 million</NUMEX> -RRB- from <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">130.1 million francs</NUMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">a year earlier</TIMEX> .
     <ENAMEX TYPE="PER_DESC">Analysts</ENAMEX> said <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Hachette</ENAMEX> 's earnings in <TIMEX TYPE="DATE:DATE">the second half</TIMEX> might be boosted by a capital gain from the sale of the <ENAMEX TYPE="GPE:CITY">Paris</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="FAC_DESC:BUILDING">headquarters</ENAMEX> of a newspaper-delivery <ENAMEX TYPE="ORG_DESC:CORPORATION">company</ENAMEX> that is <NUMEX TYPE="PERCENT">49 %</NUMEX> owned by <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION:CORPORATION">Hachette</ENAMEX> .
</DOC>
<DOC>
</DOC>
